# flashcard-app-java

Name: Minh Tan Nguyen

Flashcard App:
-This application allows users to create, load, and study a deck of flashcards and also 
add or delete flashcards within a deck.
-Features: load/save/create decks, add/delete flashcards, study decks, JavaFX GUI.

CSC 205 Concepts:
-OOP design
-ArrayList data structure
-File I/O
-JavaFX GUI

Challenges:
-After learning serialization, I tried to implement it to save/load decks. 
However, I still prefer the current approach using File I/O.
-At first, I used to have an idea of having a list of decks to choose from, not just 
one deck at a time. I realized it is a big feature, and reducing it this way is more 
suitable for this project.
-This is my first time using JavaFX, so I have to learn it as I go.

The proudest aspect of this project is the GUI, which consuming most of the time implementing
this project.

Improvements:
-Add a list of decks
-Shuffle flashcards while studying
-Add a feature that keeps track of correct/incorrect flashcards. For example, cards that are 
often answered incorrectly would appear more while studying
-Better styling